Wow. What is this?
S C K T.
Took it there at 1:20 for the break of the high of day.
Oh, my god,
there's $3. What just happened?
What just happened? I got a lot filled at 1:60,
but I got nothing filled at 2 or 3 or 4 for that matter.
This is the biggest trade of the month. So.
So far. I've got no words.
It doesn't even look like it's that big
cause the big. The big move happened,
but really, it's almost a double
on. Well,
we were up over 100% the first second of the trade,
but now it's thankfully grinded back up.
Can we get back to two 50 and three?
I'm just gonna let this last little bit of runners just go
and see if we get back to three.
And there's my full exit. That trade overall was 1:24 to 2:50.
So more than 100% on the play. Unbelievable.